Welcome to Business Central. Ready to
get
started? Here's an overview of some
important first
steps. We provide a sample company named
Cronis. We've set it up with everything
you need to try things out. You get
customer, vendor, and item data
transactions ready for posting. You also
get historical data so it feels like a
real
company. When you're ready, you can
create your own company and then import
your own
data. The setup guide helps you through
the steps that are unique to your
business. There are guides for other
processes as well, but we're sticking to
the first steps
here. Enter your company name and
finalize. Once you create your company,
you can import your own data or start
from scratch.
The data migration guide makes it easy
to import data such as customers,
vendors, and items from other accounting
systems. You can import your company
data from Excel
[Music]
files. Once you're ready to use Business
Central on your own, you can turn off
the teaching tips in my
settings. We hope you're getting off to
a good start with Business Central.
Thank you for watching this video.